Very recently, Katie Davis Court was hit in the face
with a flagpole in Portland by an Antifa radical,
leaving her with a very blackened eye.
So Katie, thank you very much.
And I'd like to also say that I watched Nick.
Where's Nick?
Is Nick here?
Nick?
Hi, Nick.
That was a rough time you went through.
I watched, I hope you got my little note.
I wrote you a note.
I really appreciated that.
It helped a lot because it was a difficult situation.
It was very stressful.
And your note helped a lot, I truly appreciate it.
I thought it was terrible, actually.
I thought it was terrible.
So we'll talk about it a little bit.
Under the last administration,
the Department of Justice targeted faithful Catholics,
Christians, and patriotic parents as domestic extremists.
They said, oh, they're extreme
because they believe in God.
They're extreme because they go to a Catholic church
or evangelicals.
Everybody was under the gun.
Unless you were a really bad, sick person,
then they left you alone.
Under the Trump administration,
we're going after Antifa criminals
and all who fund and support their campaigns
are in serious trouble.
And we have a lot of records already,
a lot of surprises, a lot of bad surprises.
It's people that you would never thank.
I want to thank Attorney General Pam Bondi,
who, by the way, yesterday was incredible in Congress.
It was amazing, and she just did it from the heart.